tiktok.com 2019-06-30

# Privacy Policy | TikTok

_Last updated: February 2019_

If you are an EU resident, instead of the below, this [Privacy Policy](http://tiktok.com/en-uk/privacy-policy) shall apply. If your usual residence is in Germany, this [Privacy Policy](http://tiktok.com/de/privacy-policy) shall apply. If your usual residence is in Russia, this [Privacy Policy](https://www.tiktok.com/ru/privacy-policy/) shall apply. If your residence is in India, this [Privacy Policy](https://www.tiktok.com/hi/privacy-policy) shall apply. If your residence is in another country, and not the US, this [Privacy Policy](https://www.tiktok.com/en/privacy-policy-row) shall apply.

Welcome to TikTok (the “Platform”). The Platform is provided and controlled by musical.ly, Inc. (“musical.ly”, “we” or “us”). We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy covers the experience we provide for users age 13 and over on our Platform. For information about our under-13 experience (“Children’s Platform”) and our practices in the United States regarding children’s privacy, please refer to our [Privacy Policy for Younger Users](https://www.tiktok.com/en/privacy-policy-for-younger-users).

Capitalized terms that are not defined in this policy have the meaning given to them in the [Terms of Service](https://www.tiktok.com/i18n/terms/).

##   
What information do we collect?

We collect information when you create an account and use the Platform, such as your contact details, content you create, and your location. We also collect information you share with us from third-party social network providers, and technical and behavioral information about your use of the Platform. We also collect information contained in the messages you send through our Platform and information from your phone book, if you grant us access to your phone book on your mobile device.

### Information you choose to provide

For certain activities, such as when you register, upload content to the Platform, or contact us directly, you may provide some or all of the following information:

  * Registration information, such as age, language, and email or phone number
  * Profile information, such as name, social media account information, and profile image
  * User-generated content, including comments, photographs, videos, and virtual item videos that you choose to upload or broadcast on the Platform (“User Content”)
  * Payment information, such as PayPal or other third-party payment information (where required for the purpose of payment)
  * Your phone and social network contacts, with your permission. If you choose to find other users through your phone contacts, we will access and collect the names and phone numbers and match that information against existing users of the Platform. If you choose to find other users through your social network contacts, we will collect your public profile information as well as names and profiles of your social contacts
  * Your opt-in choices and communication preferences
  * Information to verify an account such as a form of identification
  * Information in correspondence you send to us
  * Information you share through surveys or your participation in challenges, sweepstakes, or contests such as your gender, age, likeness, and preferences.

### Information we obtain from other sources

We may receive information about you from other sources. For example, if you choose to link or sign up using your social network (such as Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, or Google), we may collect information from these third-party services, including your contact lists for these services and information relating to your use of the Platform in relation to these services.

We will also receive information about you (including age data and demographic information) from third parties (such as advertising networks and analytics providers) and from other sources, including business directories and other commercially or publicly available sources.

###   
Information we collect automatically

We automatically collect certain information from you when you use the Platform, including your IP address, location-related data (as described below), unique device identifiers, browsing history (including content you have viewed in the Platform), Cookies (as defined below), your mobile carrier, time zone setting, and mobile or device information including the model of your device, screen resolution, operating system, app and file names and types, and platform.

### Usage Information

We collect information regarding your use of the Platform and any other User Content that you generate through and broadcast on our Platform. We also link your subscriber information with your activity on our Platform across all your devices using your email, phone number, or similar information.

### Location data

We collect information about your location, including location information based on your SIM card and/or IP address. With your permission, we may also collect Global Positioning System (GPS) data.

### Messages

We collect and process, which includes scanning and analyzing, information you provide in the context of composing, sending, or receiving messages through our Service's messaging functionality. That information includes the content of the message and information about when the message has been sent, received and/or read, as well as the participants of the communication. Please be aware that messages sent to other users of our Service will be accessible by those users and that we are not responsible for the manner in which those users use or disclose messages.

### Metadata

When you upload User Content, you automatically upload certain metadata that is connected to the User Content. Metadata describes other data and provides information about your User Content that will not always be evident to the viewer. In connection with your User Content the metadata can describe how, when, and by whom the piece of User Content was collected and how that content is formatted. It also includes information, such as your account name, that enables other users to trace back the video to your user account. Additionally, metadata will consist of data that you chose to provide with the video, e.g. any hashtags used to mark keywords to the video and captions.

### Cookies

We and our vendors and service providers use cookies and other similar technologies (e.g. web beacons, flash cookies, etc.) (“Cookies”) to automatically collect information, measure and analyze which web pages you click on and how you use the Platform, enhance your experience using the Platform, improve our services, and provide you with targeted advertising on the Platform and elsewhere across your different devices. Cookies are small files which, when placed on your device, enable the Platform to provide certain features and functionality. Web beacons are very small images or small pieces of data embedded in images, also known as “pixel tags” or “clear GIFs,” that can recognize Cookies, the time and date a page is viewed, a description of the page where the pixel tag is placed, and similar information from your computer or device. By using the Platform, you consent to our use of Cookies.

Additionally, we allow our business partners, advertising networks, and other advertising vendors and service providers (including analytics vendors and service providers) to collect information about your online activities through Cookies. We link your contact or subscriber information with your activity on our Platform across all your devices, using your email or other log-in or device information. These third parties may use this information to display advertisements on our Platform and elsewhere online tailored to your interests, preferences, and characteristics. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these third parties, and the information practices of these third parties are not covered by this Privacy Policy.

## How we use your information

We use your information to fulfill and enforce our [Terms of Service](https://www.tiktok.com/i18n/terms/), to improve and administer the Platform, and to allow you to use its functionalities. We may also use your information to, among other things, show you suggestions, promote the Platform, and customize your ad experience.

We generally use the information we collect:

  * to fulfill requests for products, services, Platform functionality, support and information for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical, and survey purposes and to solicit your feedback
  * to customize the content you see when you use the Platform. For example, we may provide you with services based on the country settings you have chosen or show you content that is similar to content that you liked or interacted with
  * to send promotional materials from us or on behalf of our affiliates and trusted third parties
  * to improve and develop our Platform and conduct product development
  * to measure and understand the effectiveness of the advertising we serve to you and others and to deliver targeted advertising
  * to make suggestions and a customized ad experience
  * to support the social functions of the Platform, including to permit you and other users to connect with each other through the Platform and for you and other users to share, download, and otherwise interact with User Content posted through the Platform
  * to use User Content as part of our advertising and marketing campaigns to promote the Platform
  * to help us detect abuse, fraud, and illegal activity on the Platform
  * to ensure that you are old enough to use the Platform (as required by law)
  * to communicate with you, including to notify you about changes in our services
  * to announce you as a winner of our contest, sweepstakes, or promotions if permitted by the promotion rule, and to send you any applicable prizes
  * to enforce our terms, conditions, and policies
  * consistent with your permissions, to provide you with location-based services, such as advertising and other personalized content
  * to inform our algorithms
  * to combine all the information we collect or receive about you for any of the foregoing purposes
  * for any other purposes disclosed to you at the time we collect your information or pursuant to your consent.

## How we share your information

We are committed to maintaining your trust, and we want you to understand when and with whom we may share the information we collect. We will share your information with the following selected third parties:

  *  **Authorized third-party vendors and service providers.** We share your information with third-party vendors and service providers that help us perform our business operations, including research, payment processing and transaction fulfillment, database maintenance, contest administration, technology services, deliveries, email deployment, advertising, analytics, measurement, data storage and hosting, disaster recovery, search engine optimization, marketing, and data processing.
  *  **Business partners.** We may share your information with our business partners so that we can make you special offers via the Platform.
  *  **Corporate group.** We may share your information with a parent, subsidiary, or other affiliate of our corporate group.
  *  **Business transfers.** We may share your information in connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of a website, a merger, consolidation, asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.
  *  **Legal purposes.** We may disclose information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, legal process, law enforcement requests, legal claims or government inquiries, and to protect and defend the rights, interests, safety, and security of musical.ly Inc, our affiliates, users, or the public.
  *  **Advertisers.** We give advertisers reports about the types of people seeing their ads and how their ads are performing.
  *  **With your consent.** We may share information for any other purposes disclosed to you at the time we collect the information or pursuant to your consent.

If you access third-party services, such as Facebook, Google, or Twitter, to login to the Platform or to share information about your usage on the Platform with others, these third-party services may be able to collect information about you, including information about your activity on the Platform, and they may notify your connections on the third-party services about your use of the Platform, in accordance with their privacy policies.

If you choose to engage in public activities on the Platform, you should be aware that any information you share may be read, collected, or used by other users. You should use caution in disclosing personal information while engaging. We are not responsible for the information you choose to submit.

## Your Choices

  * You may be able to refuse or disable Cookies by adjusting your browser settings. Because each browser is different, please consult the instructions provided by your browser. Please note that you may need to take additional steps to refuse or disable certain types of Cookies. For example, due to differences in how browsers and mobile apps function, you may need to take different steps to opt out of Cookies used for targeted advertising in a browser and to opt out of targeted advertising for a mobile application, which you may control through your device settings or mobile app permissions. In addition, your opt-out selection is specific to the particular browser or device that you are using when you opt out, so you may need to opt-out separately for each of browser or device. If you choose to refuse, disable, or delete Cookies, some of the functionality of the Platform may no longer be available to you.

  * You can manage third-party advertising preferences for some of the third parties we work with to serve advertising across the Internet by clicking here and by utilizing the choices available at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> and [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).

  * Your mobile device may include a feature that allows you to opt out of some types of targeted advertising ("Limit Ad Tracking" on iOS and "Opt out of Interest-Based Ads" on Android).

  * You can opt out of marketing or advertising emails by utilizing the “unsubscribe” link or mechanism noted in marketing or advertising emails.
  * You can switch off GPS location information functionality on your mobile device if you do not wish to share GPS information.
  * If you have registered for an account you may access, review, and update certain personal information that you have provided to us by logging into your account and using available features and functionalities.
  * Some browsers transmit "do-not-track" signals to websites. Because of differences in how browsers incorporate and activate this feature, it is not always clear whether users intend for these signals to be transmitted, or whether they even are aware of them. We currently do not take action in response to these signals.

## Security

We use reasonable measures to help protect information from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. You should understand that no data storage system or transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100 percent secure. Please note that information collected by third parties may not have the same security protections as information you submit to us, and we are not responsible for protecting the security of such information.

## Children

The privacy of users under the age of 13 (“Younger Users”) is important to us. We provide a separate experience for Younger Users in the United States on the Children’s Platform, in which we collect only limited information. For more information on our United States data collection practices for Younger Users, please visit the [Privacy Policy for Younger Users](https://www.tiktok.com/en/privacy-policy-for-younger-users).

The Platform otherwise is not directed at children under the age of 13. If we become aware that personal information has been collected on the Platform from a person under the age of 13 we will delete this information and terminate the person’s account. If you believe that we have collected information from a child under the age of 13 on the Platform, please contact us at [privacy@tiktok.com](mailto:privacy@tiktok.com).

## California Residents

Once a calendar year, you may be entitled to obtain information about personal information that we shared, if any, with other businesses for their own direct marketing uses. If applicable, this information would include the categories of customer information, as well as the names and addresses of those businesses with which we shared customer information for the immediately prior calendar year. To request a notice, please submit your request to [privacy@tiktok.com](mailto:privacy@tiktok.com).

Users of the Platform who are California residents and are under 18 years of age may request and obtain removal of User Content they posted by emailing us at [privacy@tiktok.com](mailto:privacy@tiktok.com). All requests must be labeled "California Removal Request" on the email subject line. All requests must provide a description of the User Content you want removed and information reasonably sufficient to permit us to locate that User Content. We do not accept California Removal Requests via postal mail, telephone, or facsimile. We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, and we may not be able to respond if you do not provide adequate information. Please note that your request does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the material. For example, materials that you have posted may be republished or reposted by another user or third party.

## Changes

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we update the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by updating the “Last Updated” date at the top of this policy and posting the new Privacy Policy and providing any other notice required by applicable law. We recommend that you review the Privacy Policy each time you visit the Platform to stay informed of our privacy practices.

## Contact

Questions, comments and requests regarding this policy should be addressed to:

  * Musical.ly Inc. Address: Attn: TikTok Legal Department 10100 Venice Blvd, Suite 401, Culver City, CA 90232, USA
  * Email Address: [privacy@tiktok.com](mailto:privacy@tiktok.com)
